Jordan Alexis

alexisjordan842@yahoo.com | 1-646-625-8972

I have experience using programming languages such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Cloud Computing, and others to help build websites for clients or myself.

Experience using Adobe Creative Cloud applications such as Premiere, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, and XD to help make my websites and other jobs I must do.

Experience entering client information into a database, checking the information is secured and correct. Dealing with customers who need help with orders placed or account information.

Experience

Sofyware Engineer

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Unadat, New York, NY (US)

- •Led a cross-functional team to develop a dark mode for the Unadat portal site.
- •Optimized dark theme for the mobile and progressive web app.
- Coordinated efforts of the design team in devising and user testing the color scheme and functionality.
- •Debugged independent research to overcome roadblocks and obstacles.

Spring Intern Jan 2019 - May 2019

WBAI Radio 99.5FM NYC, Brooklyn, NY (US)

- Assisted in Sorting and Mailing out prizes for their WBAI Buddies.
- Managed their social media Using Hootsuite
- Assigned managing some Customer Service tasks.
- Assisted in their event calendar by using Photoshop to make the pictures for each article presentable.
- Assisted in entering important personal data for their WBAI Buddies.

Multimedia Internship Jul 2018 - Aug 2018

The Challenge Publisher Group, Brooklyn, NY (US)

- •Assisted in creating a modernized version of a newspaper called "The New American" by making it in Adobe InDesign from scratch.
- I Used Photoshop to make images given to me more presentable.
- Distributed the Newspaper to the boroughs of New York.

Office Assistant Aug 2017 - Aug 2017

SYEP, Brooklyn, NY (US)

- Assisted in handling/transferring calls to the site managers and Interns.
- Handing of entering data for payroll and time spent working at job sites.
- Handling Information to see if the applicants/Inters were still working and checking on their performance review.

Multimedia Developer Internship

Jul 2017 - Aug 2017

St. John's Recreation Center, Brooklyn, NY (US)

- Learned about Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign effectively.
- Learned how to record audio using GarageBand and using audio to create a 3-5-minute video using Windows Media Player.

Day Care Worker Jul 2014 - Aug 2014

Charles Churn Christian Academy, Brooklyn, NY (US)

- Assisted in making sure the children (5-10) went to their destinations safely.
- Assisted in making activities, organized the work and camp environment.
- Carried equipment to wherever they needed to be.

Skills & Specialization

Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Premiere, Adobe XD, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Pho, Adobelllustrator, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Outlook, HTML/CSS, PHP, Responsive Design, Data Entry, jQuery

Education

Brooklyn College

Aug 2019 - Presently Enrolled

Bachelor's Degree, Multimedia Computing and Computer Science Brooklyn, US

Borough of Manhattan Community College

Aug 2017 - May 2019

Associate degree, Multimedia Programming and Design Manhattan, US

Technical Career Institute

Jan 2017 - May 2017

Associate degree, Credits Towards Computer Systems Networking and Telecommunications Manhattan, US

Bramson Ort College

Oct 2014 - Jan 2017

Associate degree, Credits Towards Computer Information Systems (Game Design Concertation) Queens, US

Websites

https://jordan721.github.io/Jordan_Alexis/